Finding Aid for the Lou Derman Papers PASC.0099
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lou Derman papers
1944-1975
UCLA Library Special Collections
Derman, Lou
PASC.0099
16.0 Linear Feet (32 boxes and 81 bound volumes)
Lou Derman was a comedy writer whose numerous credits include co-creator and head writer of the television series Mr. Ed, and writer and producer of All in the Family. The collection consists of bound volumes of various radio and television scripts related to Dermans comedy writing career.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Donation, 1990.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9912178083606533
Biography
Lou Derman was born in (approximately) 1914 and was educated at New York University. As a television comedy writer, he was co-creator and head writer of the Mr. Ed television series (6 years), head writer of December Bride (4 years), and writer and producer of All in the Family. Derman died on February 15, 1976.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of 81 bound volumes of various radio and television program scripts related to the career of writer and producer, Lou Derman. Radio scripts from programs include Life With Luigi (September 1948 to February 1953), Our Miss Brooks (December 1953 to June 1954), Happy Island starring Ed Wynn (September 1944 to February 1945), and Let Yourself Go starring Milton Berle (March to June 1945). Television scripts from programs include December Bride (season 1954/55 to 1958/59), Mister Ed (season 1960/61 to 1965/66), The Gale Storm Show (season 1959/60), and All in the Family (July 1974 to February 1975).
Radio writers -- United States -- Archives.; Radio plays.; Television writers -- United States -- Archives.; Television plays.; Derman, Lou--Archives.
- Radio writings
  - ED WYNN SHOW (The Fire Chief)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/5/1945 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/12/1945 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/19/1945 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/26/1945 (Box 31)
  - EDDIE CANTOR SHOW (It's Time To Smile)
    Scope and Content
    Network: NBC Announcer: Harry Von Zell. Music: Leonard Sues' Orchestra.
    - Paulette Goddard, 11/28/1945 (Box 31)
      Scoe and Content Note
      With cast list. Guests, Paulette Goddard and Kenny Delmar.
    - Hildegard, 12/12/1945 (Box 31)
      Scope and Content Note
      With cast list. Guests: Hildegard and Kenny Delmar.
    - Alan Young, 12/19/1945 (Box 31)
      With cast list. Guests: Alan Young, Hildegard, Kenny Delmar.
    - [Title Unknown], 9/25/1947 (Box 31)
      With cast list. Guest: Catherine Luddy.
    - [Title Unknown], 10/2/1947 (Box 31)
      With cast list. Guest: Mrs. Bobby Woodward.
    - [Title Unknown], 10/9/1947; With cast list. (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/16/1947; With cast list. (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/23/1947 (Box 31)
      With cast list. Guest: Jimmy Durante.
  - HAPPY ISLAND (ED WYNN)
    Network: Blue Network Sponsor: Borden Stars: Ed Wynn, Minerva Pios Announcer: Paul Douglas Music: Mark Warnow and His Orchestra.
    - [Title Unknown], 9/4/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/15/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/22/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/29/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/6/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/13/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/20/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/27/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/3/1944; Missing pages. (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/17/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/24/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/30/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/8/1944; Missing pages. (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/22/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/29/1944 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/12/1945 (Box 31)
    - Lawsuit Between a Radio Crooner and a Radio Comedian, 1/15/1945 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/29/1945 (Box 31)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/15/1944 (Box 31)
  - JIM BACKUS SHOW, THE
    Network: Mutual Sponsor: Feen a Mint Cast: Jerry Hausner, Frances Robertson, Francis "Dink" Trout. Announcer: Frank Graham
    - [Title Unknown], 2/29/1948; No number. (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/7/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/14/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/21/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/28/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/4/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/11/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/18/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/25/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/2/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/9/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/16/1948 (Box 23)
    - .[Title Unknown], 5/23/1948 (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/30/1948 (Box 23)
  - KISS AND MAKE UP
    Host: Milton Berle. Orchestra leader; Harry Salter.
    Concept: Contestants were married couples who aired their grievances before a panel of audience members. The panel decided who was at fault and the penalty was to kiss and make up.
    - [Title Unknown], 7/1/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 7/15/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 7/22/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 7/29/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/5/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/12/1946 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/19/1946 (Box 30)
  - LEFTY
    - ., 3/18/1946 (Box 31)
    - ., 3/25/1946 (Box 31)
    - ., 4/1/1946 (Box 31)
    - ., 4/15/1946 (Box 31)
    - ., 4/22/1946 (Box 31)
  - LET YOURSELF GO (MILTON BERLE)
    Variety show that featured comedy and music.
    - [Title Unknown], 3/21/1945 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/28/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/11/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/18/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/25/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/2/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/9/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/16/1945 (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/23/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/30/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/6/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/13/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/27/1945; With cast list. (Box 30)
  - LIFE WITH LUIGI
    Situation comedy. Network: CBS Luigi: J. Carrol Naish.
    - Luigi Discovers America, 9/21/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/5/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/12/1948; Found under 12/28/48; with cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/19/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/26/1948; Revised - with cast list. (Box 21)
    - Finds Stolen Diamond Ring, 11/9/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - Luigi Attends PTA Meeting, 11/16/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/23/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - Luigi Joins Hospital Plan, 11/30/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - Damage Claim on Broken Mirror, 12/7/1948; With cast list. (Box 21)
    - Paul Revere, 12/14/1948; Revised - with cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/28/1948; Same as 10/12/48; with cast list. (Box 21)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/2/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - First Date With American Girl, 1/9/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Surprise Party, 1/16/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/23/1949; Revised - with cast list. (Box 24)
    - Character References, 1/30/1949; Revised - with cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Recieves Erroneous Phone Bill, 2/6/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/13/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Making a Speech With a Fever, 2/20/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Needs Driver's License, 2/27/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Income Tax Problems, 3/6/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - The Raffle, 3/13/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi's First Car, 3/20/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Goes to Dance School, 3/27/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Tries to Return a Nightgown, 4/3/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Rosa Must Lose Weight, 4/10/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Gets a Big Electric Bill, 4/24/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi Plans a Block Party, 5/1/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Luigi's Toothache, 5/8/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Super Salesman, 5/15/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - The Wedding, 5/29/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/5/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Papa's Coat Pocket, 6/12/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Pasquale's Birthday Party, 6/19/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - Life Insurance Policy, 6/26/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - July 4th Parade, 7/3/1949; With cast list. (Box 24)
    - At the Beach, 7/17/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Homesick, 7/24/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - X-Ray Pictures, 7/31/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - A Date With Shirley, 8/7/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Sore Thumb, 8/14/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - The Driver's License, 8/21/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Go West Young Man, 8/28/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Hit and Run Witness, 9/4/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Luigi Tries to Become a Singer, 9/11/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Midget Radio Lawsuit, 9/18/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Block Party, 9/25/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Stock Investments, 9/27/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Luigi Throws a Party at the Store, 10/4/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Columbus Day Play, 10/11/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/18/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - The Zoning Commission, 10/25/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Football Game, 11/1/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - No Electioneering, 11/8/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/15/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Thanksgiving Celebration, 11/22/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Money for the Kids, 11/29/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Post office Breaks Luigi's Gift, 12/6/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/13/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Pasquale Takes Luigi's Christmas Money, 12/20/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - New Year's Phone Call, 12/27/1949; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Pietro Needs an Overcoat, 1/3/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Luigi's First Citizenship Papers, 1/10/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/17/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Using Television to Increase Business, 1/24/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Flunking the Final Exam, 1/31/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - The Abraham Lincoln Letter, 2/7/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Movie Date, 2/14/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Washington Radio Contest, 2/21/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Mrs. Spaulding's Party, 2/28/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Income Tax Season, 3/7/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Big Brothers of America, 3/14/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Luigi Enlists in the Marines, 3/21/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Luigi Finds a Wallet, 3/28/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Traffic Light, 4/4/1950; With cast list. (Box 25)
    - Bosco is a Good Name, 4/11/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/18/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Donation for Gym Equipment, 4/25/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Sootho's Cough Syrup Guarantee, 5/2/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/9/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Future American, 5/16/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Taking a Picture of Rosa, 5/23/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi's Antiques are Auctioned Off, 5/30/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Party Line Troubles, 6/6/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/13/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi Has a Fire in the Store, 8/15/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Business Trip to Buffalo, 8/22/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/29/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi Sells Ice Cream, 9/5/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi is Lonely, 9/12/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Crusade for Freedom Speech, 9/19/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Torlley Transfer, 9/26/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi Gives Blood, 10/3/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - A Day in New York With Frank Sinatra, 10/10/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Pasquale Hires a Tutor, 10/17/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Antique Dealers of America Association, 10/24/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Right to Vote Taken Away, 10/31/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - Luigi Opens His Barber Shop, 11/7/1950; With cast list. (Box 26)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/21/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Non Counted in the Census, 11/28/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Lost in Chicago, 12/5/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Joins The Record Collector's Club, 12/12/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - A Christmas Present for Pasquale, 12/19/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - A Visit From the Immigration Service, 12/26/1950; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Ice Skating at the Lake, 1/2/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Queen Sheba's Iceberg, 1/9/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Deposits a California Check, 1/16/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Refuses to Talk to Pasquale, 1/23/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Graduating From 1A to 1B, 1/30/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Finds Out He Has Tonsilitis, 2/6/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Has His Tonsils Removed, 2/13/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Puts a Negro in His Play, 2/20/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Becomes a Gas Station Attendant, 2/27/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - The Mail Order Suit, 3/6/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/13/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - The Spring Walk, 3/20/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - April Fool's Joke, 3/27/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/3/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/10/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Bosco Pasquale Lifetime Shoelace Company, 4/17/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Mrs. Spaulding Resigns, 4/24/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - A Date With the Librarian, 5/1/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Horse and Wagon Delivery Service, 5/8/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - I Want to Be an American Day, 5/15/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Rosa's Make Over for the Antique Dealer's Dance, 5/22/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - How to Make Minestrone Soup, 5/29/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/5/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Becomes a Soda Jerk, 6/12/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Decides to Paint His Own Safety Zones, 6/19/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Luigi Throws a Party for His Salesmen, 6/26/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - The Fourth of July Parade (repeat broadcasst), 7/3/1951; With cast list. (Box 27)
    - Shultz and Olson Not in Luigi's Class, 8/28/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Naming the O'Reilly's Baby Contest, 9/4/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi's Block Party, 9/11/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi Isn't in the Phone Book, 9/18/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Go West Young Man, 9/25/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Mama Thinks Luigi is a Millionaire, 10/2/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/9/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi's Dun and Bradstreet Rating, 10/16/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi, the Square Dance Caller, 10/23/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Trick or Treat, 10/30/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi Opens Up a New Antique Store, 11/6/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Mrs. Spaulding Off For a Week, 11/13/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Thanksgiving Dinner, 11/20/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/27/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/4/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/11/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/18/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - A Christmas Present for Pasquale, 12/25/1951; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/1/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Luigi Takes Rosa to the Movies, 1/8/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Rosa Attends Luigi's Night Class, 1/15/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Rosa Goes to the Head of the Class, 1/22/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - The High Standard of Living, 1/29/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Homesick, 2/5/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - The Toledo Weighing Machine, 2/12/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/19/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Joins Local Civil Defence Group, 2/26/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Pasquale Threatens to Evict Luigi, 3/4/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Income Tax Problems, 3/11/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/18/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - Essay Contest, 3/25/1952; With cast list. (Box 28)
    - April Fools Joke, 4/1/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - Easter Birthday Party, 4/8/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - Luigi Can't Sleep, 4/15/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - Takes a Date to Antique Dealers Dance, 4/22/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/29/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/6/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/13/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/20/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/27/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/12/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/19/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 8/26/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/2/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/9/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/16/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/23/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 9/30/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/7/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/14/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/21/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 10/28/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/11/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/18/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 11/25/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/2/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/9/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/16/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 12/23/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - .[Title Unknown], 12/30/1952; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - Luigi Leaves for California, 1/6/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/13/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/20/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/27/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/3/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/10/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/17/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/24/1953; With cast list. (Box 29)
  - MIGHTY CASEY, THE
    - ., 3/8/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 3/15/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 3/22/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 3/29/1947; Revised. (Box 21)
    - ., 4/12/1947; Revised - with list of characters. (Box 21)
    - ., 4/19/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 4/26/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 5/3/1947; With list of characters (Box 21)
    - ., 5/10/1947; Revised. (Box 21)
    - ., 5/24/1947; Revised - with list of characters. (Box 21)
    - ., 5/31/1947; Revised. (Box 21)
    - ., 6/7/1947 (Box 21)
    - ., 6/21/1947 (Box 21)
  - OUR MISS BROOKS
    Situation comedy. Star: Eve Arden Network: CBS Sponsor: Colgate Palmolive Peet.
    - Poison Ivy, 1954 October 4; no number; with cast list (Box 22)
    - Plaque for Mr. Conklin, 1954 October 11; no number; with cast list (Box 22)
    - Mr. Boynton's Barbeque, 1954 October 18; no number; with cast list (Box 22)
    - Conklin the Bachelor, 12/13/1953; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - Christmas Gift Mixup, 12/20/1953; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - Miss Brooks Writes About a Hobo, 12/27/1953; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 1/3/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - Hobbies, 1/10/1954; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - Selling the House Next Door, 1/17/1954; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - Foreign Teachers, 1/24/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - Four Fiancees, 1/31/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/7/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/14/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/21/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 2/28/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/7/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/14/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/21/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 3/28/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/4/1954; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/11/1954; First draft - with cast list - no number. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/18/1954; First draft - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/25/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/2/1954; Revised - with cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/16/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/23/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/30/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/6/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/13/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/20/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
    - [Title Unknown], 6/27/1954; With cast list. (Box 22)
  - ROBERT Q. LEWIS'S LITTLE SHOW
    - ., (No date) (Box 30)
    - ., 5/3/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 5/24/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 5/31/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 6/7/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 6/13/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 6/20/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 6/27/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 7/4/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 7/11/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 7/18/1947 (Box 30)
    - ., 7/25/1947 (Box 30)
  - THAT'S RICH
    Situation comedy. Starring: Stan Freberg. Network: CBS
    - [Title Unknown], 4/9/1954; With cast list. (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/23/1954; With cast list. (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 4/30/1954; With cast list. (Box 23)
    - [Title Unknown], 5/27/1954; With cast list - rehearsal/tape date. (Box 23)
- Television writings
  - ALL IN THE FAMILY
    - ARCHIE IS MISSING!,., 7/19/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - ARCHIE STRIKES,., 8/2/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - ARCHIE UNDERFOOT,., 8/14/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - EDITH THE JOB HUNTER,., 8/21/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - LONGEST KISS, THE,., 7/29/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - WHERE'S ARCHIE?,., 7/12/1974; Final draft (Box 13)
    - ALL'S FAIR,., 12/19/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - AMELIA'S DIVORCE,., 1/8/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - ARCHIE AND THE MIRACLE,., 10/30/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - ARCHIE AND THE QUIZ,., 1/22/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - ARCHIE'S CONTRACT,., 11/13/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - ARCHIE'S HELPING HAND,., 10/2/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - ARCHIE'S RAISE,., 9/18/1974; Final draft (Box 14)